$CCOR_CompleteCraftingOverhaul	Complete Crafting Overhaul
$CCOR_CompleteCrafting	Complete Crafting
$CCOR_Skyrim	Skyrim
$CCOR_Dawnguard	Dawnguard
$CCOR_Hearthfire	Hearthfire
$CCOR_Dragonborn	Dragonborn
$CCOR_EnableAll	ENABLE ALL
$CCOR_DisableAll	DISABLE ALL
$CCOR_RecipeDisplay	Recipe Display
$CCOR_CraftingOptions	Crafting Options
$CCOR_Learning&XP	Learning & XP
$CCOR_Mining&Materials	Mining & Materials
$CCOR_Tempering&Enchanting	Tempering & Enchanting
$CCOR_Miscellaneous	Miscellaneous
$CCOR_ModOptions	Mod Options
$CCOR_NoModOptions	No mod options currently available
$CCOR_Vanilla	Vanilla
$CCOR_Unleveled	Unleveled
$CCOR_Specific	Specific
$CCOR_MoreOre	More Ore
$CCOR_MuchMoreOre	Much More Ore
$CCOR_FasterMining	Faster Mining
$CCOR_FasterMiningMoreOre	Faster Mining and More Ore
$CCOR_SlowerMining	Slower Mining
$CCOR_SlowerMiningMuchMoreOre	Slower Mining and Much More Ore
$CCOR_UseCustomSettings	Use Custom Settings
$CCOR_5:1	5:1
$CCOR_PerPerk	Per Perk
$CCOR_3:1	3:1
$CCOR_DisplayRecipesFrom	Display Recipes from
$CCOR_AnimatedArmory	Animated Armoury
$CCOR_Bandoliers	Bandoliers, Bags and Pouches
$CCOR_BeyondSkyrim	Beyond Skyrim
$CCOR_BookofSilence	Book of Silence
$CCOR_Campfire	Campfire
$CCOR_Cloaks	Cloaks of Skyrim
$CCOR_CreationClub	Creation Club
$CCOR_HeavyArmory	Heavy Armoury
$CCOR_ImmersiveArmors	Immersive Armours
$CCOR_ImmersiveJewelry	Immersive Jewellery
$CCOR_ImmersiveWeapons	Immersive Weapons
$CCOR_JaysusSwords	JaySuS Swords
$CCOR_WinterIsComing	Winter Is Coming
$CCOR_AdditionalMods	Additional Mods with CCOR Support
$CCOR_CraftingMenuFilters	Crafting Menu Filters
$CCOR_CraftingCategories	Crafting Categories
$CCOR_ItemTypeFilters	Item Type Filters
$CCOR_ExtendedJewelryTypes	Extended Jewellery Types
$CCOR_BreakdownRecipes	Breakdown Recipes
$CCOR_InventoryConditions	Inventory Conditions
$CCOR_AdditionalDisplayOptions	Additional Display Options
$CCOR_UseInventoryConditions	Use Inventory Conditions
$CCOR_CraftDaedricItemsOnlyatNight	Craft Daedric Items Only at Night
$CCOR_RecipeSupport	Support included for
$CCOR_BothSexes	Both Sexes
$CCOR_FemaleOnly	Female Characters
$CCOR_MaleOnly	Male Characters
$CCOR_NonLoreFantasyItems	Non-Lore Fantasy Items
$CCOR_RecipeComplexity	Recipe Complexity
$CCOR_Immersive	Immersive
$CCOR_Simplified	Simplified
$CCOR_FurandHideRecipes	Fur and Hide Recipes
$CCOR_Generic	Generic
$CCOR_Specific	Specific
$CCOR_JewelryCrafting	Jewellery Crafting
$CCOR_PreciousMetals	Precious Metals
$CCOR_SkillRequirementforSilver	Skill Requirement for Silver Smithing
$CCOR_SkillRequirementforGold	Skill Requirement for Gold Smithing
$CCOR_CraftDawnguardItems	Craft Dawnguard Items
$CCOR_AtAnyForge	At Any Forge
$CCOR_FortDawnguard	Fort Dawnguard
$CCOR_CrossbowsandBolts	Crossbows and Bolts
$CCOR_DawnguardOnly	Dawnguard Only
$CCOR_ThroughoutSkyrim	Throughout Skyrim
$CCOR_AdditionalItems	Additional Items
$CCOR_MoreJewelry	More Jewellery
$CCOR_UnenchantedVariations	Unenchanted Variations
$CCOR_ArtifactReplicas	Artifact Replicas
$CCOR_MatchingSetCirclets	Matching Set Circlets
$CCOR_BreakdownEquipment	Breakdown Equipment
$CCOR_AtSmelter	At Smelter
$CCOR_AtTanningRack	At Tanning Rack
$CCOR_ProtectFavoritedItems	Protect Favorited Items
$CCOR_ProtectEquippedItems	Protect Equipped Items
$CCOR_SmithingExperience	Smithing Experience
$CCOR_Forge	Forge
$CCOR_TanningRack	Tanning Rack
$CCOR_Smelter	Smelter
$CCOR_Mining	Mining
$CCOR_SmithingXPBarFix	Update XP Bar Immediately
$CCOR_LearntoCraft	Learn to Craft
$CCOR_EnableLearningRecipes	Enable Learning Recipes
$CCOR_LearningPointsrequiredtoCraft	Learning Points required to Craft
$CCOR_AlternateExperienceFormula	Alternate Experience Formula
$CCOR_UseAlternateXPFormula	Use Alternate XP Formula
$CCOR_VanillaFlatXPAmount	Vanilla Flat XP Amount
$CCOR_BonusMultiplier	Bonus Multiplier
$CCOR_BonusExponent	Bonus Exponent
$CCOR_AccumulatedLearningPoints	Accumulated Learning Points
$CCOR_AncientNordLearning	Ancient Nord Learning
$CCOR_FalmerLearning	Falmer Learning
$CCOR_FalmerHeavyLearning	Falmer Heavy Learning
$CCOR_ForswornLearning	Forsworn Learning
$CCOR_MiningPresets	Mining Presets
$CCOR_AnimationCyclesperdrop	Animation Cycles per drop
$CCOR_AttackStrikesperdrop	Attack Strikes per drop
$CCOR_Oresperdrop	Ores per drop
$CCOR_Dropspervein	Drops per vein
$CCOR_MiningMakesNoise	Mining Makes Noise
$CCOR_Gemstones	Gemstones
$CCOR_GemList	Gem List
$CCOR_GemChance	Gem Chance
$CCOR_FlawlessGemChance	Flawless Gem Chance
$CCOR_DisableNewGems	Disable New Gems
$CCOR_RenameMaterials	Rename Materials
$CCOR_CorundumtoCopper	Corundum to Copper
$CCOR_MalachitetoGlass	Malachite to Glass
$CCOR_MalachitetoMoldavite	Malachite to Moldavite
$CCOR_QuicksilvertoMithril	Quicksilver to Mithril
$CCOR_Firewood	Firewood
$CCOR_Firewoodperchop	Firewood per chop
$CCOR_Maxperactivation	Max per activation
$CCOR_Smelting	Smelting
$CCOR_IngotProduction	Ingot Production
$CCOR_CharcoalProduction	Charcoal Production
$CCOR_VariableTemperingStrength	Variable Tempering Strength
$CCOR_EnableTemperingAdjustments	Enable Tempering Adjustments
$CCOR_BaselineAdjustment	Baseline Adjustment
$CCOR_Daggers	Daggers
$CCOR_Bows	Bows
$CCOR_TwoHandWeapons	Two-Hand Weapons
$CCOR_LightArmor	Light Armour
$CCOR_NonmetallicArmors	Non-metallic Armours
$CCOR_Shields	Shields
$CCOR_Cuirasses	Cuirasses
$CCOR_Gauntlets	Gauntlets
$CCOR_VariableEnchantmentStrength	Variable Enchantment Strength
$CCOR_EnableEnchantingAdjustments	Enable Enchanting Adjustments
$CCOR_Clothing	Clothing
$CCOR_Body/Torso	Body/Torso
$CCOR_Head/Hands/Feet	Head/Hands/Feet
$CCOR_AllJewelry	All Jewellery
$CCOR_ExpensiveJewelry	Expensive Jewellery
$CCOR_ExquisiteJewelry	Exquisite Jewellery
$CCOR_Daggers	Daggers
$CCOR_Bows	Bows
$CCOR_OneHandWeapons	One-Hand Weapons
$CCOR_TwoHandWeapons	Two-Hand Weapons
$CCOR_Accessories	Accessories
$CCOR_SilverBonus	Silver Bonus
$CCOR_SilverArmorBonus	Silver Armour Bonus
$CCOR_SilverWeaponBonus	Silver Weapon Bonus
$CCOR_EnchantmentBonus	Enchantment Bonus
$CCOR_StalhrimBonus	Stalhrim Bonus
$CCOR_GildedArmorBonus	Gilded Armour Bonus
$CCOR_LeveledItems	Leveled Items
$CCOR_UpgradeLeveledItems	Upgrade Leveled Items
$CCOR_UpgradeviaCrafting	Upgrade via Crafting
$CCOR_AutoUpgrade	Auto Upgrade
$CCOR_LevelUpSpell	Level Up Spell
$CCOR_DistributeinLists	Distribute in Lists
$CCOR_UpgradingItems	Upgrading Items
$CCOR_UnarmedAttackBonus	Unarmed Attack Bonus
$CCOR_FistsofSteelLight	Fists of Steel - Light
$CCOR_Troubleshooting	Troubleshooting
$CCOR_EnableNotifications	Reactivate Notifications
$CCOR_Updated	Updated
$CCORDesc_SkyrimRecipes	Toggles the visibility of all base Skyrim recipes in the forge and tanning rack menus.
$CCORDesc_DawnguardRecipes	Toggles the visibility of recipes added by Dawnguard in the forge and tanning rack menus.
$CCORDesc_HearthfireRecipes	Toggles the visibility of recipes added by Hearthfire in the forge menu.
$CCORDesc_DragonbornRecipes	Toggles the visibility of recipes added by Dragonborn in the forge and tanning rack menus.
$CCORDesc_CreationClubRecipes	Toggles the visibility of recipes added by Creation Club mods in the crafting menu.
$CCORDesc_CCORRecipes	Toggles the visibility of crafting recipes added by Complete Crafting Overhaul.  This does not affect tempering, breakdown, or rough gem recipes.  It DOES toggle learning recipes, matching set circlets, unenchanted faction gear, artifact replicas, and added jewellery recipes.
$CCORDesc_MODSupportedRecipes	Toggles the visibility of recipes added by other mods and patches with built in CCOR-support that are not listed here separately.
$CCORDesc_MODHeavyArmory	Toggles the visibility of recipes added by Heavy Armoury in the crafting menu.
$CCORDesc_MODImmersiveArmors	Toggles the visibility of recipes added by Immersive Armours in the crafting menu.
$CCORDesc_MODImmersiveWeapons	Toggles the visibility of recipes added by Immersive Weapons in the crafting menu.
$CCORDesc_MODImmersiveJewelry	Toggles the visibility of recipes added by Immersive Jewellery in the crafting menu.
$CCORDesc_MODBandoliers		Toggles the visibility of recipes added by Bandoliers - Bags and Pouches.
$CCORDesc_MODCloaksofSkyrim	Toggles the visibility of recipes added by Cloaks of Skyrim.
$CCORDesc_MODCampfire		Toggles the visibility of recipes added by Campfire.
$CCORDesc_MODJaysusSwords	Toggles the visibility of recipes added by JaySuS Swords.
$CCORDesc_MODWinterisComingCloaks	Toggles the visibility of recipes added by Winter is Coming - Cloaks.
$CCORDesc_SkyUICategories	Enables Crafting Category filters within the crafting menus.
$CCORDesc_SkyUIItemTypes	Enables Item Type filters within the crafting menus.
$CCORDesc_SkyUIBreakdown	Enables the option to toggle the Breakdown recipes from within the tanning rack and smelter menus.
$CCORDesc_SkyUIInventory	Enables the option to toggle the Inventory Conditions from within the crafting menus.
$CCORDesc_SkyUIExtJewelry	Enables additional Item Type filters for jewellery added by other mods, such as earrings and bracelets.
$CCORDesc_InventoryConditions	Adds conditions to certain recipes that check whether you have at least some of the necessary crafting components in your inventory; this can help to reduce recipe bloat in the crafting menu.  These conditions are most prevalent on jewellery recipes, but occur on some other recipes as well.  Disabling this option does not remove inventory conditions on breakdown recipes, learning recipes, or basic material recipes, such as those for crafting ingots or leather.
$CCORDesc_DaedricAtNight	Allows Daedric items to only be crafted at night, defined as the hours between 9pm and 5am.
$CCORDesc_SexSupportOption	Displays armour and clothing recipes that include meshes to support wear by all characters.  This setting can be used to display mod-added items that only offer support for female or male characters.
$CCORDesc_NonLore	Displays highly fanciful items and items that may deviate strongly from established lore.\nDoes not affect any vanilla items.
$CCORDesc_Complexity	Choose whether certain recipes should be simplified to their primary ingredients, or whether they should include additional ingredients like pelts or wood in an attempt to more closely represent their in-game appearance.
$CCORDesc_FurPlate	Choose whether recipes with fur components will use generic Fur Plate or whether they will require specific hides.
$CCORDesc_DawnguardItems	Choose whether Dawnguard faction items can be crafted at any forge or if they can only be crafted at Fort Dawnguard.  In either case you must complete the quest requirements before you can craft Dawnguard items.
$CCORDesc_DawnguardCrossbows	Choose whether basic steel crossbows and bolts will be available throughout Skyrim or only available for members of the Dawnguard.
$CCORDesc_SilverSmithing	The Smithing skill level required in order to craft silver items.
$CCORDesc_GoldSmithing	The Smithing skill level required in order to craft gold items.
$CCORDesc_MoreJewelryItems	Enables recipes for additional jewellery items with gemstone combinations not present in the vanilla game, as well as allowing these items to show up in leveled lists.
$CCORDesc_UnenchantedVersions	Enables recipes for unenchanted versions of relatively common items that are typically found only as enchanted versions in the game.  This includes unenchanted versions of divine amulets and faction armours.
$CCORDesc_ArmoredCirclets	Enables recipes for armoured circlets that fulfill the Matching Set perk requirements and have stats identical to their corresponding helmets.  Most of these recipes require that you have the respective helmet before you can craft the circlet.
$CCORDesc_ArtifactReplicas	Enables recipes for unenchanted replicas of unique or artifact caliber items. This includes unenchanted versions of daedric artifacts, Nightingale items, and Ancient Falmer armour.
$CCORDesc_BreakdownSmelter	Allows metallic armour, weapons, and misc items to be broken down into ingots at a smelter.
$CCORDesc_BreakdownTanningRack	Allows leather and hide items to be broken down into fur plate and leather strips at a tanning rack.
$CCORDesc_ProtectEquipped	The number of similar items that will be protected from being broken down when one is equipped.  For example, if you often dual-wield with identical weapons, then you can set this value to 2 to protect both items. Or if you want to be able to break down equipped items, then set this value to 0 to disable all protection for equipped items.
$CCORDesc_ProtectFavorite	The number of similar items that will be protected from being broken down when one is favorited.  For example, if you often dual-wield with identical weapons, then you can set this value to 2 to protect both items. You can also protect an entire stack of items by favoriting one of them, and setting this value much higher.  Set this value to 0 to disable all protection for favorited items.
$CCORDesc_VanillaFlatXP	The vanilla smithing formula includes a flat 25 points of XP for every item crafted.  This setting allows you to adjust the flat XP amount.  By reducing this value, it serves to further remove the benefit of crafting many cheap items.
$CCORDesc_AlternateXP	Enables an alternate formula for calculating XP gained from crafting items at the forge and tanning rack.  This new formula rewards more XP points for items that have not been crafted before, and decreasing amounts of XP for each additional time an identical item is crafted.
$CCORDesc_AlternateXPMult	The amount of smithing experience you gain when using the forge is multiplied by this amount.  If Alternate XP Formula is enabled, then this value will determine how much XP you'll continue to receive after crafting 3 copies of an item.  A value of 0.1 means that very little additional XP will be awarded when crafting 4 or more copies of an item.  A value of 1 means that you will receive full vanilla XP regardless of the number of copies crafted.
$CCORDesc_AlternateXPBonus	This number controls the size of the bonus XP awarded for the first 3 copies of each item crafted.  Higher numbers result in increased XP for the first 3 copies.  Setting this value to 0 will result in no bonus XP.  A value of 53 will result in bonus amounts of +150/+100/+50 for an item which would give 100 XP per copy if using the vanilla formula.
$CCORDesc_AlternateXPExp	This number determines how sharply the XP amounts will drop off after an additional copy has been crafted.  Lower values will flatten this curve and provide only a moderate decrease in XP per copy crafted.
$CCORDesc_TanningRackXP	Modifies the amount of Smithing experience gained when using the tanning rack. Experience is calculated by vanilla formulas and varies depending on the item's gold value.  Setting this option to 0 will result in no Smithing experience; a value of 0.5 is 50% experience; and a value of 1.0 is 100% experience.
$CCORDesc_SmelterXP	Modifies the amount of Smithing experience gained when using the smelter. Experience is calculated by vanilla formulas and varies depending on the item's gold value.  Setting this option to 0 will result in no Smithing experience; a value of 0.5 is 50% experience; and a value of 1.0 is 100% experience.
$CCORDesc_MiningXP	The amount of experience gained in smithing skill whenever the player mines ore. This is the actual amount of experience, not a percentage.  Setting the value at 0 means that mining has no effect on smithing skill. Vanilla: 0. Recommended settings if using this feature: 15-30.
$CCORDesc_SmithingXPBarFix	This forces the Smithing XP bar to update immediately after crafting an item, but may not function properly with some mods or if you have high script latency. Disable this option if you experience issues. Gamepads not currently supported.
$CCORDesc_LearningEnabled	Enables certain equipment types to be learned by deconstructing them at the forge.
$CCORDesc_LearningPointsRequired	The number of learning points required before those items can be crafted.  Deconstructing most items will result in either 25 or 50 learning points.  Setting this value to '0' will remove the learning requirement and allow you to automatically craft these items once you've met any perk requirements. Default: 100 (between 2 to 4 items).
$CCORDesc_LearningFalmer	Total accumulated points toward learning to craft Falmer armour & weapons.\nThe Elven Smithing perk is required to learn and to craft Falmer items.
$CCORDesc_LearningAncientNord	Total accumulated points toward learning to craft Ancient Nord armour & weapons.
$CCORDesc_LearningFalmerHeavy	Total accumulated points toward learning to craft Falmer Heavy armour.\nThe Dwarven Smithing perk is required to learn and to craft Falmer Heavy items.\nFalmer Hardened items require the Ebony Smithing perk.
$CCORDesc_LearningForsworn	Total accumulated points toward learning to craft Forsworn armour & weapons.
$CCORDesc_MiningPresets	Adjust mining speed and the number of ores received from mining.\nVanilla = 3 ores in 9 strikes. More Ore = 6 ores in 18 strikes. Much More Ore = 24 ores in 72 strikes.\nFaster Mining = 3 ores in 3 strikes. Faster Mining and More Ore = 6 ores in 3 strikes.\nSlower Mining = 3 ores in 18 strikes. Slower Mining and Much More Ore = 24 ores in 144 strikes.
$CCORDesc_MiningAnimationCycles	Number of animation cycles per ore drop. One animation cycle consists of 3 strikes. Vanilla: 1 (3 strikes)\nAnimations per Drop X Drops per Vein X 3 = The total number of animated strikes that it will take to fully deplete the vein.
$CCORDesc_MiningAttackStrikes	Number of attack strikes per ore drop. Vanilla: 3\nAttack Strikes per Drop X Drops per Vein = The total number of attack strikes that it will take to fully deplete the vein.
$CCORDesc_MiningOreAmount	The amount of ore received per drop. Vanilla: 1
$CCORDesc_MiningOreTotal	Total number of drops before mineral vein is depleted. Vanilla: 3\nOres per drop X Drops per Vein = The total number of ores acquired before depleting the vein.
$CCORDesc_MiningDetection	Adds a small detection event when the player mines ore deposits.
$CCORDesc_OreIngotRatio	The ratio of ore to ingots produced at a smelter. The 5:1 ratio is the recommended setting.  Prices and weight have been balanced around the 5:1 ratio and will NOT change if you select other options.  However, for those who simply can't tolerate this, there is a 3:1 option.  There is also a perk-dependent option, which begins at a 5:1 ratio and changes to a 3:1 ratio once you've acquired the related smithing perk.
$CCORDesc_FirewoodCharcoalRatio	The ratio of firewood to charcoal produced at a smelter.
$CCORDesc_FirewoodAmount	Pieces of firewood received per chop. Vanilla: 2
$CCORDesc_FirewoodMaximum	Maximum pieces of firewood per each activation. Vanilla: 6
$CCORDesc_GemstoneDistribution	Choose the type of gemstone leveled list to associate with mining:\nVanilla = the chance of receiving more valuable gems is tied to player level.\nUnleveled = the chance of receiving more valuable gems is not dependent on player level.\nSpecific = certain gems are associated with specific types of ore and are not dependent on player level.
$CCORDesc_GemChance	Percent chance of receiving gemstones when mining. Vanilla: 10
$CCORDesc_FlawlessGemChance	Percent chance of receiving flawless gemstones when refining gems at a forge. Default: 20
$CCORDesc_DisableNewGems	Disables the new gems added by CCOR and removes them from the leveled lists for merchants, loot, and mining.
$CCORDesc_RenameCorundum	Corundum is renamed to Copper.
$CCORDesc_RenameMalachite01	Malachite Ore is renamed Raw Glass, and Refined Malachite is renamed Refined Glass.
$CCORDesc_RenameMalachite02	Malachite Ore is renamed Raw Moldavite, and Refined Malachite is renamed Refined Moldavite.
$CCORDesc_RenameQuicksilver	Quicksilver is renamed to Mithril.
$CCORDesc_EnableEnchantAdjustments	Enables you to adjust the relative strength of the enchantments placed on certain types items.
$CCORDesc_EnchantClothing	The relative strength of enchantments placed on clothing items.\nDoes not apply to Fortify Alchemy, Smithing, Light Armour or Heavy Armour enchantments.
$CCORDesc_EnchantBody	The relative strength of enchantments placed on primary body pieces, such as cuirasses and robes.\nDoes not apply to Fortify Alchemy, Smithing, Light Armour or Heavy Armour enchantments.
$CCORDesc_EnchantMinor	The relative strength of enchantments placed on hand, head, or feet pieces.
$CCORDesc_EnchantJewelry	The relative strength of enchantments placed on jewellery items.\nDoes not apply to Fortify Alchemy, Smithing, Light Armour or Heavy Armour enchantments.
$CCORDesc_EnchantJewelryExpensive	The relative strength of enchantments placed on expensive jewellery items. Expensive jewellery is defined as all jewellery worth over 300 gold.  This setting will stack with the adjustment for all jewellery.\nDoes not apply to Fortify Alchemy, Smithing, Light Armour or Heavy Armour enchantments.
$CCORDesc_EnchantJewelryExquisite	The relative strength of enchantments placed on exquisite jewellery items. Exquisite jewellery is defined as rings and necklaces worth over 700 base gold and circlets worth over 900 base gold. This setting will stack with the adjustment for all jewellery and expensive jewellery.\nDoes not apply to Fortify Alchemy, Smithing, Light Armour or Heavy Armour enchantments.
$CCORDesc_EnchantDaggers	The relative strength of enchantments placed on daggers.
$CCORDesc_EnchantBows	The relative strength of enchantments placed on bows and other ranged weapons.
$CCORDesc_EnchantOneHand	The relative strength of enchantments placed on one-handed weapons, except daggers.
$CCORDesc_EnchantTwoHand	The relative strength of enchantments placed on two-handed weapons, except bows.
$CCORDesc_EnchantAccessory	The relative strength of enchantments placed on accessories such as bags and cloaks.
$CCORDesc_EnableTemperAdjustments	Enables you to adjust the relative strength of the tempering improvements made to certain types of items.
$CCORDesc_TemperBase	This setting will adjust the strength of ALL smithing improvements.
$CCORDesc_TemperDaggers	The relative strength of smithing improvements made to daggers.
$CCORDesc_TemperBows	The relative strength of smithing improvements made to bows.
$CCORDesc_TemperTwoHand	The relative strength of smithing improvements made to two-handed weapons, except bows.
$CCORDesc_TemperLightArmor	The relative strength of smithing improvements made to all Light Armour items.  Does not apply to shields.
$CCORDesc_TemperHide	The relative strength of smithing improvements made to leather, fur, or hide armours.  This setting will stack with the Light Armour adjustment.
$CCORDesc_TemperShields	The relative strength of smithing improvements made to shields.
$CCORDesc_TemperCuirass	The relative strength of smithing improvements made to cuirasses.
$CCORDesc_TemperGauntlets	The relative strength of smithing improvements made to gauntlets.
$CCORDesc_SilverWeaponBonus	The percent increase in damage dealt by Silver weapons when used against the undead or werewolves.  Changing this value to a multiplier allows it to benefit from weapon improvements, player skill, and fortify bonuses.  Setting this value to 0 results in the vanilla default of straight +20 damage.
$CCORDesc_SilverArmorBonus	The percent damage reduction against attacks from undead or werewolves when wearing a full set of Silver armour.  This does not apply to any vanilla armours, but may apply to mods with CCOR-support.  Setting the value to 0 will result in no bonus for silver armour.
$CCORDesc_GoldenArmorBonus	Percentage bonus applied to Resist Fire enchantments when placed on Golden armour.  This does not apply to any vanilla armours, but may apply to mods with CCOR-support.  Setting the value to 0 will result in no bonus.
$CCORDesc_StalhrimEnchantBonus	Bonus applied to Frost enchantments when placed on Stalhrim items. The vanilla bonus is 25% but internal text indicates it was probably intended to be 10%.
$CCORDesc_UpgradeLeveledItemsNow	Upgrades all unique leveled items that are currently in the player's inventory to match the player's current level.  Items will lose any smithing improvements when they are upgraded.
$CCORDesc_UpgradeLeveledSpell	Adds the Upgrade Leveled Items spell to the player's spell list.
$CCORDesc_UpgradeLeveledAuto	Runs the Upgrade Leveled Items spell automatically whenever the player levels.\nThe spell will not run if the player is in combat when they level.
$CCORDesc_UpgradeLeveledRecipes	Enables crafting recipes that allow you to upgrade any unique leveled items you have.  These recipes will appear in the Miscellaneous category at the forge once your character reaches the appropriate level to upgrade the item.
$CCORDesc_FistsofSteelLight	Enabling this option allows the Fist of Steel perk to also apply an appropriately scaled unarmed damage bonus when wearing light armour gloves or gauntlets.  Works for all vanilla items, and for any WACCF-compatible modded items that have the correct keywords.
$CCORDesc_EnableNotifications	Use after updating to CCOR version 1.2 in order to reactivate on-screen notifications.
$CCOR_SmithingXPBarFix	Update XP Bar Immediately